[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the kanji '引っ越します' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ひっこしします"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the kanji '通います' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "かよいます"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the kanji '側' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "そば, がわ"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the kanji '頃' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ころ"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the kanji '言葉' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ことば"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the kanji '接頭辞' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "せっとうじ"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the kanji '接尾辞' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "せつびじ"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the kanji '大学校' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "だいがっこう"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the kanji '新自転車' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しんじてんしゃ"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the kanji '不親切な' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ふしんせつ"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the kanji '御住所' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ごじゅうしょ"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the kanji '研究所' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "けんきゅうじょ"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the kanji '映画館' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "えいがかん"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "How is the kanji '音楽家' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "おんがくか"
    },
    {
        "id": "15",
        "question": "How is the kanji '動物園' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "どうぶつえん"
    },
    {
        "id": "16",
        "question": "How is the kanji '動物' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "どうぶつ"
    },
    {
        "id": "17",
        "question": "How is the kanji '園' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "えん"
    },
    {
        "id": "18",
        "question": "How is the kanji '図書館' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "としょかん"
    },
    {
        "id": "19",
        "question": "How is the kanji '古本屋' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ふるほんや"
    },
    {
        "id": "20",
        "question": "How is the kanji '新聞社' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しんぶんしゃ"
    },
    {
        "id": "21",
        "question": "How is the kanji '不有名' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ふゆうめい"
    },
    {
        "id": "22",
        "question": "How is the kanji '御飯' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ごはん"
    },
    {
        "id": "23",
        "question": "How is the kanji '不人気' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ふにんき"
    },
    {
        "id": "24",
        "question": "How is the kanji '新公園' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しんこうえん"
    },
    {
        "id": "25",
        "question": "How is the kanji '銀行家' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ぎんこうか"
    },
    {
        "id": "26",
        "question": "How is the kanji '作家' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "さっか"
    },
    {
        "id": "27",
        "question": "How is the kanji '新作分' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しんさくぶん"
    },
    {
        "id": "28",
        "question": "How is the kanji '所' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ところ"
    },
    {
        "id": "29",
        "question": "How is the kanji '狭くて、小さいところ' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "せまくて, ちいさいところ"
    },
    {
        "id": "30",
        "question": "How is the kanji '住所' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "じゅうしょ"
    },
    {
        "id": "31",
        "question": "How is the kanji '近所' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "きんじょ"
    },
    {
        "id": "32",
        "question": "How is the kanji '名所' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "めいじょ"
    },
    {
        "id": "33",
        "question": "How is the kanji '特別な仕事すること' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "とくべつなしごとすること"
    },
    {
        "id": "34",
        "question": "How is the kanji '研究所' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "けんきゅうじょ"
    },
    {
        "id": "35",
        "question": "How is the kanji '市役所' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しやくしょ"
    },
    {
        "id": "36",
        "question": "How is the kanji '刑務所' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "けいむしょ"
    },
    {
        "id": "37",
        "question": "How is the kanji '場' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ジョウ・ば"
    },
    {
        "id": "38",
        "question": "How is the kanji '人が集まる所です' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ひとがあつまるところです"
    },
    {
        "id": "39",
        "question": "How is the kanji '会場' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "かいじょう"
    },
    {
        "id": "40",
        "question": "How is the kanji '浴場' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "よくじょう"
    },
    {
        "id": "41",
        "question": "How is the kanji '市場' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "いちば"
    },
    {
        "id": "42",
        "question": "How is the kanji '何か行うことです' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "なにかおこなうことです"
    },
    {
        "id": "43",
        "question": "How is the kanji '劇場' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "げきじょう"
    },
    {
        "id": "44",
        "question": "How is the kanji '式場' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しきじょう"
    },
    {
        "id": "45",
        "question": "How is the kanji '戦場' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "せんじょう"
    },
    {
        "id": "46",
        "question": "How is the kanji '区' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "く"
    },
    {
        "id": "47",
        "question": "How is the kanji '土地を分けたところ' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "とちをわけたところ"
    },
    {
        "id": "48",
        "question": "How is the kanji '学区' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "がっく"
    },
    {
        "id": "49",
        "question": "How is the kanji '特区' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "とっく"
    },
    {
        "id": "50",
        "question": "How is the kanji '新宿区' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しんじゅくく"
    },
    {
        "id": "51",
        "question": "How is the kanji '地' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "チ・ジ"
    },
    {
        "id": "52",
        "question": "How is the kanji '地面や土地' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ちめんやとち"
    },
    {
        "id": "53",
        "question": "How is the kanji '借地' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しゃくち"
    },
    {
        "id": "54",
        "question": "How is the kanji '墓地' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ぼち"
    },
    {
        "id": "55",
        "question": "How is the kanji '山地' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "さんち"
    }
]